Stephen Jay Gould Papers, 1899-2004
Stanford University Libraries.
- Series 3. Manuscripts
  - Subseries 1. Books
    - Ontogeny & Phylogeny
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, figures and correspondence (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 2 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 3 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 4 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 5 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 6 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Notes (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Bibliography (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Tables (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, annotated design proofs (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, correspondence (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, research - notes on the theory of heterochrony (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, reviews (2 folders)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, research - reprints and articles (3 folders)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, acknowledgments (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapters 1-2 (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 3 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 5 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 6 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 7 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 8 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 9 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 10 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Chapter 11 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Notes (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Bibliography (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proof, Glossary (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, galley proofs (miscellaneous) (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, reviews (2 folders)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, clippings (Box 356, Folder 1)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, publicity (Box 356, Folder 2)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, reports on manuscript (Box 356, Folder 3)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, annotated partial typescript
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, dust jacket mock-up (Box 359, Folder 8)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, annotated partial typescript
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, annotated partial typescript (Box 362, Folder 1)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, index cards (Box 362, Folder 2)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, clippings and reviews (Box 372, Folder 3-4)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, figures (Box 372, Folder 5-8)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, reviews and clippings (Box 459, Folder 1)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, computer data from cards (Box 515, Folder 15)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, reviews (Box 614, Folder 7)
      - Ontogeny and Phylogeny, figures (Box 691, Folder 2)
    - Ever Since Darwin: Reflections in Natural History
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript, Prologue (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescripts and articles, Darwin's Delay (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated articles, Darwin's Sea Change, or Five Years at the Captain's Table (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated articles, Darwin's Dilemma: The Odyssey of Evolution (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, Darwin's Untimely Burial (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescripts and articles, A Matter of Degree (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescripts and articles, Bushes and Ladders in Human Evolution (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, The Child as Man's Real Father (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, Human Babies as Embryos (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and article, The Misnamed, Mistreated and Misunderstood Irish Elk (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated articles, Organic Wisdom, or Why Should a Fly Eat Its Mother from Inside (Box 148, Folder 11)
      - Ever Since Darwin, typescript, Of Bamboos, Cicadas and the Economy of Adam Smith (Box 148)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript, article, and galley, The Problem of Perfection, or How can a Clam Mount a Fish on Its Rear End? (Box 148, Folder 13)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, The Pentagon of Life (Box 148, Folder 14)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, An Unsung Single-Celled Hero (Box 148, Folder 15)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, Is the Cambrian Explosion a Sigmoid Fraud? (Box 148, Folder 16)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, The Great Dying (Box 148, Folder 17)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, The Reverend Thomas' Dirty Little Planet (Box 148, Folder 18)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, Uniformity and Catastrophe (Box 148, Folder 19)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, Velikovsky in Collision (Box 148, Folder 20)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript, article, and galley, The Validation of Continental Drift (Box 148, Folder 21)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, Size and Shape (Box 148, Folder 22)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, Sizing Up Human Intelligence (Box 148, Folder 23)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, History of the Vertebrate Brain (Box 148, Folder 24)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescripts and galley, Planetary Sizes and Surfaces (Box 148, Folder 25)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, On Heroes and Fools in Science (Box 148, Folder 26)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, Posture Maketh the Man (Box 148, Folder 27)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and article, Racism and Recapitulation (Box 148, Folder 28)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, The Criminal as Nature's Mistake, or the Ape in Some of Us (Box 148, Folder 29)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and article, Why We Should Not Name Human Races - A Biological View (Box 148, Folder 30)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, The Nonscience of Human Nature (Box 148, Folder 31)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescripts and articles, Racist Arguments and IQ (Box 148, Folder 32)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, Biological Potentiality vs. Biological Determinism (Box 148, Folder 33)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and articles, So Cleverly Kind an Animal (Box 148, Folder 34)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript and notes, Epilogue (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Ever Since Darwin, index cards, Bibliography (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - Ever Since Darwin, typescript, Bibliography (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Ever Since Darwin, typescript and correspondence, Index (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - Ever Since Darwin, figures (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - Ever Since Darwin, figures (Box 585, Folder 3)
      - Ever Since Darwin, figures (transparencies) (Box 149, Folder 6)
      - Ever Since Darwin, book contract (Box 149, Folder 7)
      - Ever Since Darwin, correspondence (Box 149, Folder 8)
      - Ever Since Darwin, notes (Box 149, Folder 9)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescripts and articles from Natural History Magazine (miscellaneous) (Box 149, Folder 10)
      - Ever Since Darwin, annotated typescript (2 folders)
      - Ever Since Darwin, galley proofs (miscellaneous) (Box 149, Folder 13)
      - Ever Since Darwin, dust jackets and correspondence (Box 149, Folder 14)
      - Ever Since Darwin, dust jacket and proof (Box 149, Folder 15)
      - Ever Since Darwin, camera copy proof (3 folders)
      - Ever Since Darwin, reviews (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - Ever Since Darwin, publicity clipping (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - Ever Since Darwin, design proofs (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - Ever Since Darwin, reviews (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - Ever Since Darwin, dust jacket (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Ever Since Darwin, reviews and clippings (Box 371, Folder 3)
      - Ever Since Darwin, reviews and clippings (Box 457, Folder 16)
      - Ever Since Darwin, figures, includes prints and negatives (Box 613, Folder 2)
      - Ever Since Darwin, reviews (Box 613, Folder 3)
    - The Panda's Thumb
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated typescript and articles (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - The Panda's Thumb, design proofs (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - The Panda's Thumb, galley proofs, Introduction, Prologue, Chapters 1-7 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - The Panda's Thumb, galley proofs, Chapters 8-15 (Box 151, Folder 6)
      - The Panda's Thumb, galley proof, Chapters 16-21 (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - The Panda's Thumb, galley proof, Chapters 22-31 (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (first pass), Introduction, Prologue, Chapters 1-4 (Box 152, Folder 3)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (first pass), Chapters 5-23 (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (first pass), Chapters 24-31, Bibliography, Index (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (second pass), Introduction, Prologue, Chapters 1-4 (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (second pass), Chapters 5-11 (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (second pass), Chapters 12-20 (Box 152, Folder 8)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated article, Shades of Lamarck (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated article, Caring Groups and Shelfish Genes (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated typescript, Piltdown Revisited (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated typescripts and correspondence, Dr. Down's Syndrome (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated article, The Episodic Nature of Evolutionary Change (Box 153, Folder 5)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated article, Return of the Hopeful Monster (Box 153, Folder 6)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated article, The Great Scablands Debate (Box 153, Folder 7)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated article, A Quahog is a Quahog (Box 153, Folder 8)
      - The Panda's Thumb, index cards, Bibliography (Box 153, Folder 9)
      - The Panda's Thumb, figures (Box 153, Folder 10)
      - The Panda's Thumb, correspondence (2 folders)
      - The Panda's Thumb, notes (Box 153, Folder 13)
      - The Panda's Thumb, miscellaneous typescripts and notes (Box 153, Folder 14)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated typescript/pasteup (4 folders)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated typescript, Index (Folder 1)
      - The Panda's Thumb, annotated figures and captions with correspondence (Folder 2)
      - The Panda's Thumb, index cards, miscellaneous notes (Folder 3)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (second pass), Chapters 21-28 (Box 157, Folder 1)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (second pass), Chapters 29-31, Bibliography, Index (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - The Panda's Thumb, reviews (Box 157, Folder 3)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (out for o.k.), Introduction, Prologue, Chapters 1-8 (Box 157, Folder 4)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (out for o.k.), Chapters 9-16 (Box 157, Folder 5)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (out for o.k.), Chapters 17-25 (Box 157, Folder 6)
      - The Panda's Thumb, master galley proof (out for o.k.), Chapters 26-31, Bibliography (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - The Panda's Thumb, page layout design (Box 157, Folder 8)
      - The Panda's Thumb, publicity (Box 362, Folder 3)
      - The Panda's Thumb, clippings and reviews (Box 373, Folder 1-2)
      - The Panda's Thumb, reviews and clippings (Box 459, Folder 2)
      - The Panda's Thumb, reviews (Box 614, Folder 8)
      - The Panda's Thumb, Panda's Thumb Artwork, includes photographs (Box 614, Folder 9)
      - The Panda's Thumb, figures and artwork (oversize) (Box 585, Folder 4)
    - The Mismeasure of Man
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Front Matter, Chapters 1-2 (Box 155, Folder 1)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Chapters 3-4 (Box 155, Folder 2)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Chapter 5 (Box 155, Folder 3)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Chapter 6 (Box 155, Folder 4)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Chapter 7, Bibliography (Box 155, Folder 5)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript (3 folders)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, partial galley proof, Pages 1-16 (Folder 1)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, galley proof, excerpt published in Science Digest (Folder 2)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, correspondence (Folder 3)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, publicity (Folder 4)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, figures and correspondence (Folder 5)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, partial annotated typescript, Chapter 5 (Folder 6)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, research and notes (Folder 7)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, figures (photographs and negatives) (Folder 8)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, galley proof, 1981 Jun 13 (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, galley proof (2 folders), 1981 Jun 13
      - The Mismeasure of Man, galley proof (3 folders), 1981 Jul 13
      - The Mismeasure of Man, galley proof (3 folders), 1981 Dec 8
      - The Mismeasure of Man, galley proof, Index (Box 158, Folder 9)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, research and notes (Box 264, Folder 3)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, comments and correspondence (Box 264, Folder 4)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, typescript, Index (Box 325, Folder 1)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, research and notes (Box 325, Folder 2)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, figures (Box 325, Folder 3)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript (Box 325, Folder 4)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Chapter 2 (Box 325, Folder 5)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Chapter 3 (Box 325, Folder 6)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, cover art (Box 354, Folder 1)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, correspondence (Box 354, Folder 2)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, correspondence (Box 354, Folder 3)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, notes (Box 354, Folder 4)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, Morton (Box 354, Folder 5)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, publicity (Box 354, Folder 6)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, cover galley proof (Box 354, Folder 7)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript Thoughts at Age Fifteen (Box 354, Folder 8)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated photocopy of partial text (Box 354, Folder 9)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, research materials (4 folders)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, research materials
      - The Mismeasure of Man, galley proof (2 folders)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, research materials (Box 359, Folder 7)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, research materials (2 folders)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, miscellaneous (Box 361, Folder 11)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, clippings and reviews (Box 372, Folder 1-2)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Age-Old Fallacies of Thinking and Stinking (Box 446, Folder 1)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Ghosts of Bell Curves Past (Box 446, Folder 2)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, typescript, Racial Geometry (Box 446, Folder 3)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, research material (Box 446, Folder 4)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Chapter 5 (Box 446, Folder 5)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Chapter 2 (Box 446, Folder 6)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, typescript, Table 3-2 (Box 446, Folder 7)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, partial annotated typescript (Box 446, Folder 8)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, typescript (3 folders)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, reviews and clippings (Box 458, Folder 19)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, reviews and clippings (Box 458, Folder 20)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, annotated typescript, Thoughts at Age Fifteen (Box 458, Folder 21)
      - The Mismeasure of Man, dust jacket (Box 515, Folder 16)
    - A View of Life
      - A View of Life, typescript, Taxonomy: The Science of Classification (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - A View of Life, reviewer comments, Taxonomy: The Science of Classification (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - A View of Life, reviewer comments, Natural Selection as Evolutionary Mechanism (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - A View of Life, correspondence (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - A View of Life, correspondence, notes (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - A View of Life, partial typescripts and notes (Box 213, Folder 6)
      - A View of Life, typescript, The Ordering of Life (Box 213, Folder 7)
      - A View of Life, partial galley proof (Box 213, Folder 8)
      - A View of Life, typescript, The Ordering of Life (Box 213, Folder 9)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Evolution and the History of Life (Box 213, Folder 10)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Natural Selection as an Evolutionary Mechanism (Box 213, Folder 11)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Evolution in Populations (Box 213, Folder 12)
      - A View of Life, typescript, The Origin and Diversification of Kingdoms (Box 213, Folder 13)
      - A View of Life, partial typescript (Box 213, Folder 14)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Taxonomy: The Science of Classification (Box 213, Folder 15)
      - A View of Life, partial typescript (2 folders)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Ecology: The Interaction of Organisms and Environments (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - A View of Life, typescripts, notes, reviewer comments (4 folders)
      - A View of Life, reviewer comments, Ecology: The Interaction of Organisms and Environments (2 folders)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Blood and Immunity (Box 214, Folder 11)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Hormones: Chemical Messages (Box 214, Folder 11)
      - A View of Life, typescript, correspondence, Transport and Filtration of Body Fluids (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - A View of Life, typescript, correspondence, Life (Box 215, Folder 2)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapters 2-4 (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapters 5-7 (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapters 2-7 (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - A View of Life, typescript, correspondence, Chapters 8-9 (Box 215, Folder 6)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapters 10-12 (Box 215, Folder 7)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapters 1-3 (Box 215, Folder 8)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapters 16, 22 (Box 215, Folder 9)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 17 (Box 215, Folder 10)
      - A View of Life, partial typescripts (Box 215, Folder 11)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapters 8, 10 (Box 215, Folder 12)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 17 (Box 215, Folder 13)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 13 (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 14 (Box 259, Folder 2)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 15 (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 16 (Box 259, Folder 4)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 17 (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 18 (Box 259, Folder 6)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 25 (Box 259, Folder 7)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 27 (Box 259, Folder 8)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 28 (Box 259, Folder 9)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 29 (Box 259, Folder 10)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 30 (Box 259, Folder 11)
      - A View of Life, figure captions (Box 259, Folder 12)
      - A View of Life, figure captions (Box 259, Folder 13)
      - A View of Life, figure captions (Box 259, Folder 14)
      - A View of Life, typescripts, Introduction sections (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Glossary (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - A View of Life, proofs (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - A View of Life, partial proof (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - A View of Life, correspondence (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - A View of Life, permissions forms for figures (Box 260, Folder 6)
      - A View of Life, permissions, photographs (Box 260, Folder 7)
      - A View of Life, photographs and research from Andrew H. Knoll (Box 260, Folder 8)
      - A View of Life, publicity (Box 260, Folder 9)
      - A View of Life, reviews (Box 260, Folder 10)
      - A View of Life, correspondence (Box 325, Folder 7)
      - A View of Life, correspondence (Box 325, Folder 8)
      - A View of Life, annotated typescript, Chapters 1-7 (Box 326, Folder 1)
      - A View of Life, annotated typescript, Chapters 5-6 (Box 326, Folder 2)
      - A View of Life, partial typescript (Box 326, Folder 3)
      - A View of Life, proof, preliminary design (Box 326, Folder 4)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Infinity (Box 326, Folder 5)
      - A View of Life, annotated typescript, Chapters 7-8 (Box 326, Folder 6)
      - A View of Life, annotated typescript, Chapter 16 (Box 326, Folder 7)
      - A View of Life, partial typescript, Chapter 9 (Box 326, Folder 8)
      - A View of Life, partial typescript, Chapter 5 (Box 326, Folder 9)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 6 (Box 326, Folder 10)
      - A View of Life, typescript, Chapter 21 (Box 326, Folder 11)
      - A View of Life, notes (Box 326, Folder 12)
      - A View of Life, partial galley proof (Box 359, Folder 1)
      - A View of Life, partial galley proof and figures (Box 359, Folder 2)
      - A View of Life, figures (Box 359, Folder 3)
      - A View of Life, annotated galley proof (Box 359, Folder 4)
      - A View of Life, reviews (Box 363, Folder 7)
    - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes: Further Reflections in Natural History
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, galley proof (3 folders)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, master galley proof (first pass) (3 folders)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, master galley proof (second pass) (4 folders)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, master galley proof (confirmation) (Box 353, Folder 5)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, publicity (Box 353, Folder 6)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, reviews (Box 353, Folder 7)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, Clippings and Reviews (Box 370, Folder 1-2)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, Figures (Photographs and Negatives) (Box 370, Folder 3)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, Phyletic Size Decrease in Hershey Bars (Box 370, Folder 4)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, Science and Jewish Immigration (Box 370, Folder 5)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, Hyena Myths and Realities (Box 370, Folder 6)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, A Hearing for Vavilov (Box 370, Folder 7)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, Worm for a Century, and All Seasons (Box 370, Folder 8)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, Agassiz in the Galapagos (Box 370, Folder 9)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, The Sinkstones of Oeningen (Box 370, Folder 10)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, Hutton's Purpose (Box 370, Folder 11)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, The Titular Bishop of Titiopolis (Box 370, Folder 12)
      - Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes, The Guano Ring (Box 370, Folder 13)